[music]
Hey,
hey, hey.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Baby, baby.
>> [music]
>> Hey.
[music]
>> All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful Friday afternoon. God bless
everybody. [music] And Bitcoin is is
taking a major dump today. We got some
strange news about a
sudden price crash. Massive surprise
[music] Bitcoin attack.
In fact, it turns out here that um
over $40 million in Bitcoin was stolen
from hundreds of separate wallets that
their owners had thought were secure.
In a matter of minutes, attackers
drained some 500 cold card hardware
wallets that mostly use Signal Signature
Security. That's pretty crazy, man.
[music] Uh, I feel really sorry for
these people. My heart goes out. My
heart goes out to people who had their
crypto on a cold wallet
[music] and yet it was hacked. Man, that
is crazy, man. Nothing is secure, guys.
Nothing is secure,
honestly. Like, my heart goes out to
these people. I know what it's like to
have your wallet drained, but I don't
know what it's like to have a cold
wallet drained. Praise God. I hope I
never do. That must be the the most
[music] horrible, sickening feeling that
you could possibly imagine.
All right. Is it fake news?
All right. I hope it's fake. [music] I
hope it's fake.
I hope it's fake, but I'm not sure. But
anyway, Bitcoin has gotten a significant
move to the downside. Whether or not
it's related to the hack,
we can't really know for certain.
But one thing we can know for certain is
this. The Bitcoin price indeed has
dropped below
the PC of the range. There's no hiding
it anymore. There's no even pretending
like it's not. Are we going down to 60K?
We had a 4hour bullish divergence right
here that didn't really give us a higher
high. That's not a good sign. We got to
give a major shout out to everybody in
the chat right now. First of all, major
shout out to Jason Casper. Jason Casper
launched Bitcoin at $132,000.
He tried to long $126,000, but he used
Michael Sailor's broker and there was
some serious slippage. [music]
Big shout out to Mr. Jinx who says,
"Doc, the goat, this chop city pays off,
mate. My favorite." Shout out to Gety,
M9Q,
and Tomaash
breaking the worst hardware wallet hack
in history, Bitcoin history. 38 million
drained from 500 wallets in 25 minutes.
The attacker never touched a single
device. That is some scary stuff, man.
Like, honestly,
that is some scary stuff. Like, what the
actual? What the actual, man? That is
crazy. Shout out to Mr. Jinx. He says,
"Come on, Jay. Don't hide. We need you."
Big shout out to Krypto Coons holding it
down with Zerch.
Shout out to I enjoy being shout out to
Beluga the cat. Shout out to Calritos
YouTube. Long from 64. Dang, bro. Well,
that's not the worst place to long. I
think I long from around there, [music]
too. Where did I long?
I longed from
63 around there.
I longed from 635 twice. I longed from
63.5 twice
both times. Eh, not the worst. I longed
from 64,
got wrecked. I longed from 65.8, got
wrecked. 65, got wrecked. 64.8.
Yeah, you know, I I I I've had some I've
had some wreckage up in here, man. I've
had some wreckage, if you guys know what
I mean. If you know what I mean.
Yeah. So, it's been some chip choppity
chip chop for sure. Shout out to J Boy
Bullish. What's going on, bro?
Uh, shout out to JJ MC D and Doc the
Goat and Johnny Mack Attack. Well, well,
well, Bitcoin. Big shout out to Crypto
Crank. He says, "We long from 62300 with
every account. A little biased right
now. The bottom is in." All right.
Bottom's in, says Crypto Crank. Let's uh
I honestly personally haven't looked at
the chart all day. So that's what I hope
to do now. I hope to look at the chart
right now and see like what's going on.
So Senor's also long from 62
uh.5. [music]
All right. 62.5.
All right. All right. Well, I hope the
bottom's in now. That would be nice.
That would be quite nice. Let's uh pop
on over to the chart and see what's
going on here.
All right. So,
let's go ahead and take a look here at
what we've got growing. Oh, man. Okay.
So, we are at the value area low of this
range.
Value area low of this range. We have
taken a little bit of liquidity from
624.
And let's see how is the chart looking
right now.
I mean, potential bullish div on the 4
hour.
Uh bullish div on the 1 hour, but money
flow eh
it's decent. Let's check out our
24-minut. 24-minut to me doesn't look
like the bottom is in. I got to be
honest, the 12minut to me,
maybe maybe
you know maybe the bottom might be in
[music] on the 12m minute, but it's it's
honestly not looking the best on some of
these higher time frames. I will say
this though, after a drop like this, it
would be very easy for us to come back
to 60 63.4. It would be like extremely
easy for us to just right there. You
know what I mean? That would be pretty
dang easy. Even if the bottom's not in
heading into a weekend with low volume,
that'll be an easy squeeze with the
cheese, baby. An easy squeeze with the
cheese.
You know [music] what I'm saying? So,
let's see. Let's see what happens here.
We are changing market structure on the
12minute. We are changing market
structure [music] on the 10 minute here.
We had a little support resistance flip.
We done came back and tested it. Let's
check out the VWOPS today. We are below
the VWOP. Man, we could e we could
easily just squeeze right up to VWOP
right now. You know, it looks like she
kind of wants to Let's check out the
order flow
and see what's up with the flow, baby.
[music]
Wow. Oh my goodness. Whoa.
Wow.
All right. You know what's crazy is we
have seen so many longs open up here.
A billion volume right here in this
candle on an increase of open interest.
A billion volume right here. Shorting
like crazy. You know, interestingly
enough, with all this volume, it's
pretty evenly spread out between longs
and shorts. We have positive delta at
the lows. We have buyers stepping in,
[music] but nonetheless, there are many,
many shorts. I mean, think about it. Out
of a billion dollars worth of volume,
there's only 86 million more
longs than shorts, right? That's that's
less than 10%.
That's pretty crazy. So,
yeah, that is pretty crazy. So, yeah, a
lot of shorts here and a lot of shorts
probably could absolutely get wrecked on
the way up.
>> [music]
>> So,
look at these shorts that have opened up
here. It's quite interesting. And
[music]
yeah. Yeah, maybe we get a little bit of
a squeeze coming on up there. That would
be quite interesting as well. And it
would not surprise me.
And here's the thing.
Let's come back to the chart. Obviously,
I would really like to see $60,000. that
that is the target that I would prefer
most to see here. If we go ahead and we
pull our [music] fib, let's pull the fib
here. Oh, wow. We're bouncing from the
786. Okay. Yeah, this very well could be
a significant bounce area. Look at this.
We're bouncing from our 786 value area
low combo CDW. It's actually a triple
confluence right here. Could very easily
give us the move back up to at least the
VWOP. And if we're trading the range and
you're trading the local range,
honestly,
you know, something like this is not so
far out of the question. You know,
something like this is not that far out
of the question.
All right. Shout out to real to true.
Um,
yeah, we CDW the lows right there for
sure. You know what? I'm I'mma fire off
a little bit of a long trade right now
myself. You know what? Going to take a
little bit of a long here. Let's pop on
in.
All right, we've got a long trade.
It's a small position cuz it's a big
stop loss.
Let's put a stop loss in here.
Yeah, we we'll risk two grand on this
trade.
All right, let's see what happens with
this this baby that we've got here. All
right, we got ourselves a little bit of
a baby trade going on here. [music] All
right, a little bit of a baby trade.
Let's see what happens. What wallet
hack? So, there was a wallet hack.
There was a wallet hack [music]
where uh cold card wallet, which I had
never heard of. Um, but apparently it's
a cold hardware wallet
and [music]
600 Bitcoin were stolen from hundreds of
separate wallets that obviously the
owners thought were secure. In a matter
of minutes, 500 cold card hardware
wallets that were mostly single
signature security had been affected by
a bug that meant the wallet used
predictable softwarebased key generation
seated by chip data rather than a
sophisticated randomness generator. Man,
man, I feel for these people so much,
guys. Like, I feel for them so much.
I have I [music] have
obviously had my share of
wallet drains.
[music]
You know, I know what it's like. It It's
It's a horrible horrible feeling.
[music] It must be even worse when you
when you think that you're doing your
due diligence to secure
your [music] assets, right?
like when you're when you're doing your
due diligence to secure the assets
and then it gets hacked. Anyway, that is
crazy.
Shout out to Buen, man. Buyen, what's
going on, bro? [music] It's good to see
you here, man.
Big shouts to Buen. What's going on,
bro?
Um,
yeah, that's what happened with the
wallet [music] hack.
Now, I got a plan, Senor. Look, I got a
plan. CDW the low. We got some bull divs
on the 12. [music] We're bouncing from
the 786. We're bouncing from the value
area low.
Simple invalidation which is below the
low. [music] And you know we got
ourselves a decent risk-to-reward right
here. Almost a 4 to one coming back up
to value area high. If we squeeze over
the weekend, if we reclaim the VWOP,
[music]
we could come back up. We could come
back up. This is not the worst. We'll
see what happens here. Senor, [music]
look, maybe I've been getting a little
loose in my old age, guys. Actually,
I'll admit it. I've been getting loose
in my old age with this stuff. [music]
Man, I got to hone back in. I got to
hone back in.
I really got to hone back in. [music]
You know,
there's several YouTubers explaining how
to do it, says Doc [music] the Goat. I
don't really know what we're talking
about, Dr. Goat. Um,
I'll bet they use AI for the attack.
Yeah. Yeah.
No, it's a cold wallet. I get I mean
that's what that's what they say. Like
that's the thing. Like that's what they
say. I mean obviously [music] I can't
know for certain whether it's a hot or a
cold wallet.
Uh for sure, but it claims to be a cold
wallet. And whatever the case, it just
does really suck for the people who what
the heck for the people who,
you know, put their money on what they
thought was a cold wallet, even if it
turns out not to be. Like man, that just
sucks. I I feel for them so bad, you
know.
So, basically, out of an abundance of
caution, Coin Kite [music] is warning
all users who generated a seed phrase
using MK3 on version 4.01 on March 2021
or any subsequent version, [music] their
funds may be at risk.
We were unaware of the bug until today,
they added, advising users to proceed
calmly, verify every step, and move
their funds to a new wallet.
Updating firmware does not repair a seed
phrase that was generated by affected.
[music] So, it's the seed phrase itself
that was generated by
I I I guessed
um
by the firmware instead of using like
a dual secure element.
Oh man.
So that sucks. That really sucks for
these people, man. Honestly, what the
heck? Can you believe this? I can't
believe this. This guy also can't
believe this.
Look at this. Would you look at this?
What? What the heck? You know, there's
been some strange things of foot today.
I can't I can't take screenshots the
same way I used to. I wonder if my
MacBook Pro updated itself or something.
Trump's low approval rating is getting
even worse.
Nothing like Forbes website articles.
You know what I'm saying?
It's pretty crazy.
Um,
yeah. So, man, that sucks. That really
does suck.
Um,
check out strategy. All right, let's
check out strategy. What's the reason
for this Bitcoin long? Um well, we have
we have come to a 786 the value area
low. We took some liquidity.
Um we got a swing failure pattern. We
have
not the best looking divergences,
but honestly,
just because we had such a big drop and
we stayed down here so much today and
there's so much volume down here, it
seems very probable that we at least get
a squeeze up to 634.
So, that's why. Plus, you know, look,
what's a YouTube stream without a
freshy? Let's be honest. What is a
YouTube stream without a freshy?
Especially on a Friday, you know,
especially on a Friday.
Um,
no, you cannot change your seed phrase.
You need to make a new wallet with a
with a new seed phrase. [music]
I am pulling that fib for the 786 from
the low that we put in over here,
right here [music] on the um
on the 6th of July.
>> [music]
>> 6th of July.
Yep. From 6th of July to the high. So,
basically, I'm looking at this whole
channel and analyzing the uh the old
Fibonacci.
The old Fibonacci
Patchy [music] the pirate. The Fibonacci
the pirate.
Um
yeah, you're right, CryptoCank. I got to
lock it in, man.
Um,
yeah. Let's check out Micro Strategy.
Let's check out MSTR.
Micro Strategy
doesn't look like it's doing very much
to be honest with you.
Yeah, it doesn't really look like it's
doing much at all to be honest with you.
In fact,
it hasn't it literally has done anything
since, you know, June. June, we've been
doing nothing here. We do have bullish
divergences. You know, for me, I would
prefer I would honestly prefer not to
reclaim this box yet. I would prefer to
get one more drive to the downside
coming to around the $50 zone. [music] I
would love that. I think that, you know,
it could be really nice for a bottom,
right?
>> [music]
>> So obviously this is not to time scale,
but something like this back test the
value area high of that previous range.
I would I would really love some kind of
catastrophic bottom signal for this bare
market. I would hate if we just got a
nothing got a nothing bottom. [music]
Nothing worse than a nothing bottom. You
know what I mean?
You know,
[music]
I was thinking it would crash all the
way down. Yeah, it's very possible that
we see Micro Strategy crash all the way
down. It depends really on what happens.
Like we would need some
we need some serious changes to come on
in in this crypto market, guys. Just a
quick reminder that Bitbase
I guess I can't remind you
cuz the picture can't be accessed, but
Bitbase is giving away $500 a week.
Blow fin is giving away $2,000 a week.
So if [music] you're in the market for
winning money every week,
$2,500 worth of prize money being given
away every week if you sign up to Blowin
and or Bitbase. Also, a quick reminder,
Klein Funding, if you're looking for a
prop firm, I've got 15% discounts. Link
in the description. Big shout out to
Klein Funding. And big shout out to
Antarctic as well. You know, got got to
give a shout out to Antarctic with those
low fees if you sign up using my link.
All my exchanges, guys, sport low fees.
They sport the low fees. You know what I
mean? [music] Who got hacked? 500
wallets, apparently.
500 wallets apparently.
So
yeah, that's that's not good. That that
man,
I know I keep saying it, but I really
feel for these people because it
cuz I, you know, it hits it hits me. It
hits me cuz I I know the feeling of of
getting your wallet drained, but when I
got my wallet drained, it's like, well,
I kind of deserved it because everyone
says, you know, keep your money on a
cold wallet. Keep it on a cold wallet.
And I was keeping on a hot wallet. So,
you know, that was dumb. At least I can
say I made the mistake and I got what I
deserved. But you're keeping your stuff
on a cold wallet.
The last thing you're thinking [music]
is that that you're vulnerable,
you know, and so you you took the due
diligence. You thought you were secure.
Oh, man.
Man, my heart goes out to these people,
guys. It [music] really does.
I'm telling you,
let's [music] take a look at Etherum.
All right,
let's take a quick look at Etherum. See
how ETH is doing here. I think ETH is
still holding above the PC macro here.
Let's pull it.
Bam. Yeah, we're still holding above PC
macro. We still have confirmed bull divs
on ETH.
you know, ETH is looking ETH is is not
looking the most bearish, you know, and
and back to Bitcoin real quick. I I do
have to say that so long as we're
holding the $60,000 value area low of
the range, I would not be surprised I
would not be surprised if we don't
eventually make our way up to here,
right? I would not be surprised if we
don't eventually make our way up to here
and just trade [music] the range. That
would be pretty cool. I don't know if
it's going to happen now. I would I
would [music] prefer another low. I
really would prefer another low. You
know, this daily once this daily gives
the green dot here, which it almost did,
by the way. But once the daily does give
this green dot, I'd say that's pretty
surefire.
Pretty sure fire to say, yeah, that the
higher low is in. That's how I'm looking
at it. You know, any giveaways for me
today?
I don't know yet. How many viewers do we
have? 500.
I don't know. Let's see. Like, can we
smash up the likes? Can Can you guys
give me a reason to do a giveaway today?
[laughter]
It is interesting how many alts were
pumping yesterday before the liquidity
grab. It does make it seem suspicious.
Almost like it's a like, you know, some
kind of coordinated big money [music]
attack. You know what I'm saying?
Preparing for war. That is very strange.
That is very strange. Where to hold your
crypto? Where it's safe. I mean,
honestly, the only real safe place to
hold your crypto is in your brain, man.
You got to memorize that private key.
That's that's really the most secure
way. And even that's not secure. You
might get hit on the head [laughter]
with a coconut balls on your head
and then your whole brain stops working.
God forbid it.
Nothing on the internet is safe, my G.
Yeah. Seriously,
whatever you do, don't do the heart goes
out to you. Hand signal might get
clipped. I don't even know what the
heart goes out to hand signal is our
pink,
you know. I really don't know. Um
I don't know.
So, let's check out this baby Bitcoin
trade here.
We're up a couple hundred. We're [music]
up a couple hundo.
We're up a couple hundo. I I can't get
mad. Honestly, I can't get mad at this
at this whole entire account so far. So
far I'm up like I'm up like 47,000
just shy of 50k and I've been trading
this since July 9th. So you know 3 weeks
47k
it's not so bad. I'll take it. I'll take
it. It ain't no crypto crank up in here.
I ain't no crypto phase in here but you
know 47k in 3 weeks. I'll honestly I'll
take it, man. I'll take it.
you know. Um, [music]
yeah. Never show your seat on a public
live stream. It's It's a good thing.
It's a good thing. For some reason, all
these photos got got rugpulled on my
computer here. I guess I must have
deleted them by [music] accident. But
yeah, never show your seed phrase on a
public library. That could get your
wallet drained, honestly. Seriously.
Yeah, they might have the tech to read
your mind, honestly. You know,
might have to tech to read your mind.
So,
but yeah, who knows what kind of weird
technology, you know, I was thinking
today. I was thinking out loud, you
know. Look, I don't take me seriously,
guys. Don't take me seriously. All
right, get your tinfoil hats on,
everybody.
Get on Get your tinfoil hats on because
here's what I was thinking. All right.
Um,
what if
All right, tinfoil of time. Seriously,
what if Bitcoin itself is a giant scam
that was created by central
intelligence, the CIA,
the NSA,
MSAD,
and all these [music]
shady institution intelligence agencies
that uh basically all this time, all
this time there's been a secret back
door to the whole algorithm and they're
just waiting for the right time to
[music] steal know how much money is in
Bitcoin right now? Like trillion dollars
or something? Wouldn't that be crazy?
But that would be a genius scam. [music]
That would be genius. And not only would
it be genius, but man, that would be
that that would be crazy, man. Imagine
if this whole thing was just a rug set
up to rug [music] everybody. Man, I
would hate if that happened, man. It
would change. It would change.
Yeah, it wouldn't really change so much
for me, honestly. It would suck though.
It would suck to wake up one morning
millions of dollars poorer. I can't
imagine that.
That would suck. All right. But
thankfully, praise the Lord, I' I'd be
all right. Unless the whole economy
crashes, you know? That's the thing.
Like, nothing's really secure, man. This
whole dang economy could just go away.
Everything could go away. The only thing
that's really secure in this life is is
your relationship with God. That's it,
man. Everything else is so
Everything else is unsecure. Not
insecure. I mean, I'm insecure.
Super insecure, but everything else is
unsecure. You know, the very the very
fact that I'm able to walk on this
treadmill right now and breathe air
is a gift from the Lord and it's not
guaranteed in the next 5 minutes. You
know, nothing's secure except your
relationship with God.
It's it's it's a sobering
a bumblebee landed on my nipple. What
the heck? See, look. Nothing's secure in
life. You think your own nipples are
secure? [music]
You think your own dang nipples are
secure? Next thing you know, there's a
bumblebee landing on your nipple trying
to sting your aoria or whatever that
thing is called. What's that thing
called? Aoria.
It's a good thing I have this bug zapper
here to zap the dang bumblebee.
Sheesh, man.
>> [music]
>> What the what the
My goodness, man. [music]
I just got aorly
assaulted here. Trying to get deep and
philosophical here and now the bees are
stinging me all over the place. Sheesh,
[music]
man.
Am I still at my mom's? [music] Of
course I am.
Of course I'm still at my mom's.
Yeah, but I don't really I don't I don't
necessarily believe that about Bitcoin,
but it wouldn't surprise me. I mean, the
fact that the dang asset pumped what
billions of percent in in in like 15
[music] years, that is a little shady.
That's a little shady. I mean, an asset
that potentially has the potential to,
you know, uproot the central banking
system is going to be allowed to pump so
much. I don't know. That is a little
shady when you think about it too much.
But
don't kill bees. Well, look, I'm usually
a big fan of bees. Don't get me wrong.
I'm a gardener. I love bees. When
they're buzzing around my zucchini
plants, pollinating the dang flowers. I
love them. All right, but here's the
thing. You're going to land on me while
I'm live streaming. You might get
zapped. All right, you might get zapped.
[music]
You know what I'm saying?
Since when do I have the bug zapper next
to my table? I always keep it here cuz
here's the thing. when you're live
streaming out in your mom's garage in
the in the hot summer sun, you're
getting sweaty and you live on a farm
uh with chickens and all that stuff,
man. There are some flies out there. You
know, there are some flies out there.
Some flies out there.
[music]
Wear shirts with more fabric. Nah, I
like them fabric free, baby. I like them
fabric free. Fabrics for betas.
You know what?
Fabrics for beta mount. Here's the
thing. Here's [music] the thing. Here's
the thing.
I'm very obsessed [music] with not being
a beta and only being an alpha, which
secretly proves I am a beta cuz I have
to overcompensate,
right? But that's okay cuz that's what
the internet's for. overcompensation.
So now [music] I can't wear the fabric.
Um,
let's see.
Yeah, the queen bee will come for
revenge. Seriously.
I saved a very big bee yesterday that
nearly drowned [music] in my kid's pool.
Took over an hour for the little guy to
get back to normal. Wow, what a great
heart she got, man.
A beast sting to the nipple might turn
you into a she with uneven [laughter]
nipple diver. Yeah, seriously, you're
right. You're absolutely right. You are
absolutely right, my friend.
Um, yeah, [music]
50K or 60K. Well, here's how I'm looking
at it right now. Okay,
here's how I am looking at it right now.
The
[music]
the chart.
Wow. You know what? It looks like we're
going to squeeze up to the VWOP. It
looks like we're on a 63.4 VWOP
potentially even. Let's pull the fib
from the wick to the low
potentially even to the golden pocket.
That's going to be right at the PLC. So
63.4 [music]
to 64K. Looks like we're going to the
next place that we will probably come
[music] to
if this is not the low is going to be
our $60,000 level. If we can reclaim
64.5,
then we could go to 70 honestly. But the
problem is right now as we're chopping
around a VWOP,
which [music] we are, it becomes very
difficult to form a long-term bias,
right? [music] Forms difficult. It's
difficult to form a long-term bias. But
I do have to say in general, the key
levels are still the same. So we have 67
as key resistance. We have 60K as key
support locally right now. 60 64K is our
our important local resistance. And then
if we reclaim 67, I I still don't see
why we can't go up to the mid70s,
you know.
Uh uh. Oh [music] snap. A beast stung me
on my nipple. We did it once, we did it
twice, we got a triple. We're in the
court. We got the basketball. We
dribble. Then we're looking like we have
to scribble [music] on the paper. Got
the pen, baby. Drawing the pictures. The
Bitcoin looking so indescriptor. We
[music] don't know if we're about to
pump or dump. We're in a battle like
Camala and Donald [music] Trump. Yeah.
Big shout out to Joe Biden. What
happened to him, baby? Man, that guy be
hiding. Even though we know he's been
dead since 2019, he is a body [music]
double. You know what I mean? He got the
fake looking like the cake. Got a bake.
Just until you make it. Yeah, cuz you
know [music] you can't fake it. You got
a hole in your shirt, you better duct
tape it. Old school [music] market
coming out in the wash, baby. What do
you know? Jasper out here. Listen to my
crypto flow [music] and just sit back,
relax, and welcome to the Jason Casper
show. Got to give a big shout everyone
in the chat. Crypto prank. [music] What
about that? My man, an expert scalper.
We got to talk to put the fire [music]
back in. I got a log like a chicken pork
like the chicken baby. So dang good. Fry
the chicken finger licking baby. Got
that [music] hardboiled eggs with the
fat
cholesterol. What you think about
[music] that? H Yeah, but then the beat
drops again. We got to shout out to our
hacker friends. They bring the wallets,
man. Such [music] dang scumbags. They're
probably ugly like those old tags. We
got the bug sapper electrifying Bitcoin
price. We ain't even trying. Huh? Say
Casper, [music] we're in the house. Took
a fresh Bitcoin long. Looking for a
bounce. [music] Looking for a squeeze up
[singing] to 64.3. Got the cream cheese,
baby. Listen to me. We [music] got the
bagel. We put it on. Spread it around
and listen to the song around the town.
B Casper [music] on the treadmill. What
a clown. Can you even hear the sound?
Kaching. We're making profit. Can you
spot it? Big coin about to rock it. Then
we tippy tippy top it. makers [music]
try to drop it but then we just stop it
then reverse it like Sonic verse robotic
making profit all day Jason Casper gives
it to you straight every day I'm so
[music] serious I never play I'm so
hungry I'm eating from the trade we
taking [music] trades all day in the
garden outside jingle with the spade do
the [music] same exact way every day
could I change heck no way I'm playing
yeah we got the [music] solid gold
Insane. That's my name. J C says the
same. You know we out here playing the
game. Uh what's [music] up the telephone
just rang. Hello.
That beat gets me every time, man.
That beat gets me every single time.
You heard the beat and I was like,
there's no way he ain't about to get it
yet. Seriously, I Man, that beat gets me
every single time. Guys,
we're up 800 smackerels.
$200 to our tar.
You know,
63.4.
Let's see. Where is 63.4?
We're getting close, baby. Getting
close. We're getting close. That's what
I like the most. I'mma TP up there.
Maybe try and try and get back in at
[music] a back test of 625ish.
Let's see what happens here.
Let's see. [music] We got the VWOP at
63450.
We lost 50 viewers during the freestyle.
It happens. We lose viewers during the
freestyle. We lose view lose viewers
during the pump song. You know what? We
lose viewers in general. I mean, we lose
viewers in the bare market. I mean,
literally right now, what do I have? 500
viewers. Not even that. Not even 500
viewers, you know? But there was a time
we were we were raking in 3,000 people
every single live stream. But you know
what?
It is what it is, man. It's it's a tough
bare market out there, [music] you know.
I'm not going to blame it all on the
bare market. I'll blame it on myself,
too. I admit I'm not the most consistent
streamer YouTuber out there, you know.
But yeah, it's been tough. It's been
rough. It's been tough and rough, baby.
It's been tough and rough.
It's been tough and it's been rough out
there.
[music]
Man, I hope we hit our take profit soon,
baby. Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Yeah. Only diamonds stay for the
freestyles. I gained 50. I gained 50
when I killed the bee. Yeah, I gained 50
lbs when I killed the bee.
Why are you not singing about my
farting? You want me to sing about your
farting?
Washing wants me to sing about the
farting.
All right, let's get a good farting beat
[music] here. Uh, farted
freestyle. [music]
Boom. Bap beat. Let's see what we can
find.
Brain fart.
I don't know.
I don't know if this is going to work
out, guys. [singing and music]
>> [music]
>> What a lame beat.
I'm sorry. I can't do it. Here we go.
Fart rap instrumental.
>> I can't do it either. I'm sorry. I I
This is why I can't sing about your
fart. I can't, you know,
dark fart.
Here we go. Uh,
yeah, we got the dark fart, baby.
Uh, [music]
uh, yeah.
Uh,
yeah.
Uh, hey yo, [music] I'm an artist. They
call me J Casper art and I'm here just
to rap about my friend Spart. He's got a
washing machine. [music] Got to wash out
the clothes cuz he farts inside the
fabric. Put it on his nose. Sniff the
[music] part. The gas goes up into the
brain. So insane right in the membrane.
You had enough. We got the coffee in the
cup. The flatulence coming out. Trying
[music] to act tough. Roar. Squeezing
out the butt cheeks. Got the gas coming
out. [music] Baby got to take a peek. Is
the gas the color green? Maybe it's red.
Jay Castro, [music] he's got the bars
vision. I feel something down low in the
colon. Drake Castro, what is that guy
[music] hoping? Don't you know I got the
gas so fast? Got to let out a fart.
Hopefully it don't last. [music]
Nothing worse than when you park in the
car and it lingers as you're driving
[music] so far. And you can feel it
beating in your heart. The gas is coming
out. Baby, we stay hard on the street.
Baby, don't mess with me. Don't you know
a bark in your face and then I'll start
to flow. We got the freestyle coming out
[music] the dome. Jay Casher in the
garage at his mom's home. Please again.
What can I say? I'm cutting [music]
baby all day. Got the gas baby. Got the
flat last the Bitcoin looking [singing]
so emerit
[music]
making my intestines a little gurgly
fart. Huh? Yeah, we got [music] the dark
fart. J Cowing purple like a work of
art. Shout out to the Casper crew. Did
someone take a poop? Heck no. Just me
and you [music] farted. We farted. We
farted all day. We're coming to the
charts. Baby fart getting paid. Got to
fart cuz we eat too much fiber. [music]
The Bitcoin price about to pump a
higher. Yeah. And then we hit the tank
profit. Jason Casper coming out, baby.
Can you spot it? [music] Fighting bad
guys like Sonic versus Robotnik. Market
makers. They just tried to drop it, but
stop it. Rewind. Jay Casper looking
[music] so fine from the behind. But oh
no, what's that I smell? It smells like
a fart that came straight out of hell.
All right,
there we go.
[music]
There we go. All right. You asked for it
and we deliver.
You asked for it and we deliver.
Shout out to washing machine.
Oh [music] my goodness.
All right, let's see. Are we going to
hit our takeprofit? Let's see.
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't want to change
structure here. Let's go to the low time
frames. [music]
Uh-oh. Six minute red dot printing.
Uh-oh. 5second bear div confirmed
1 minute [music]
looking kind of nice though. Oh man, I
should probably just close this dang
trade right now.
>> Any expert TA from our our cup and
handle an analyst? Yeah, you know, you
know, [music]
you know. Shout out to Joe Kuster. He
says Hebrews 7:25, let's go. God's grace
is effectual. Amen. Amen.
Man,
[music] uh, send it to 68.3.
That's pretty high. That is pretty high.
Oh, nice. Oh, snap. Oh, no way. No way,
guys. There's a beta version of Market
Cipher B [music] that's coming out and
I'm I'm going to be beta testing it.
Cryptophase is hooking it up, baby. Man,
I can't wait.
I just got an email about it. I'll have
to do that after the stream and set this
up. Otherwise, I'll dox myself, you
know, and I don't want to dox myself.
I've already done I've already done that
enough, y'all.
You know, I've already done that enough.
Um
Okay.
Yeah, the Okay, let's see.
The 5second baritives are strong.
Yeah.
Yeah. I think I'mma close it, guys. I
think I'mma close it. I'mma close it
right now.
I closed it out for a [music] nice $750
profit. All right, that's been fun. That
was fun. And we might keep pumping.
That's okay. I'm still in my swing long
from the bottom. Can you even spot him
playing drums like John Bonham?
Um,
it's the market cipher bot. You got it,
too. Nah, man. This is some secret stuff
right now. You know, I've been just
secret stuff. But, but yeah, but yeah,
we got some secret stuff. At least at
least Cryptoface told me it was top not
top secret, but limited. Maybe. [music]
Maybe he's just blowing smoke
to make me feel special.
Cryptoface is trying to make me feel
special, you know. But um
but all right. All right. All right,
guys. I am going to head out though. God
bless everyone. I hope you have a great
weekend. May God bless you all in Jesus
name. May you and your families be super
blessed. Remember, spend some time off
the charts. Spend some time with your
family. Spend some time with God. And I
will see you guys next week. Peace.